A Guide to the Wallace Company Records, 1783-1975 (bulk 1875-1945)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Financial Records, 1840-1962., Extent: 27 boxes and 249 volumes.
  - Petty Ledger, 1892-1893 (Volume 209)
  - Petty Ledger No. 2, 1894-1895 (Volume 210)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1895-1896 (Volume 211)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1895-1896 (Volume 212)
  - Petty Ledger No. 2, 1895-1896 (Volume 213)
  - Petty Ledger, May 1897- April 1898 (Volume 214)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1898-1899 (Volume 215)
  - Petty Ledger, 1899-1900 (Volume 216)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1 February 1900 - 30 April 1901 (Volume 217)
  - Petty Ledger, 1901-1903 (Volume 218)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1901-1903 (Volume 219)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1902-1903 (Volume 220)
  - Petty Cash Book, 1903-1904 (Volume 221)
  - Petty Ledger, 1903-1905 (Volume 222)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1904-1905 (Volume 223)
  - Petty Ledger, 1905-1907 (Volume 224)
  - Petty Cash Book, 1906-1907 (Volume 225)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1907-1909 (Volume 226)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1910-1914 (Volume 227)
  - Petty Cash and Payroll Ledger, 1 January 1917 - 30 June 1919 (Volume 228)
  - Petty Cash Ledger, 1921-1922 (Volume 229)
  - Quotations (Blueprints), 1922 (Volume 230)
  - Receipts and Disbursements, Willie McCoy Time, etc, 1934, 1936 (Volume 231)
  - Record (Minute) Book, 1890-1935 (Volume 232)
  - Share Crops Ledger, 1918-1919 (Volume 233)
  - Time Book, 1878-1879 (Volume 234)
  - Time Book, 1879-1880 (Volume 235)
  - Time Book, 1880-1881 (Volume 236)
  - Time Book, 1882 (Volume 237)
  - Time Book, 1883 (Volume 238)
  - Time Book, 1884 (Volume 239)
  - Time Book, Pay Roll, Card Book, 1885-1894 (Volume 240)
  - Time Reports, 16 March 1920 - 15 September 1920 (Volume 241)
  - Time Reports, 16 September 1920 - 31 December 1920 (Volume 242)
  - Time Reports (Dover), 3 January 1921- 30 April 1921 (Volume 243)
  - Time Reports (Dover), 1 May 1921 - 31 August 1921 (Volume 244)
  - Time Reports, 1 September 1921 - 31 December 1921 (Volume 245)
  - Time Reports (Dover), 1 January 1922 - 15 June 1922 (Volume 246)
  - Time Reports (Dover), 16 June 1922 - 30 December 1922 (Volume 247)
- Series IV. Maps, Plans, and Drawings.
  This series contains oversize items, mostly maps and drawings, including Dover Farm plats and surveys, Butts Road drainage district blueprints, United States Department of Agriculture topographical maps, soil maps, oyster grounds maps, drawings of engines and pistons by the Wallace Brothers firm, and miscellaneous maps of the Tidewater region of Virginia. There are also Wallace Company tax and payroll records.
  - Boat and Engine Plans (Wallace Brothers) (Map-case 10, Drawer 15)
  - Butts Road Drainage District, 1927-1928 (6 Rolled Blueprints) (Map-case G-13, Drawer 8)
  - Dover Farm Blueprints (Map-case G-13, Drawer 8)
  - Maps and Plats (2 Folders) (Map-case 10, Drawer 14)
  - Pay Rolls, 1885-1889 (3 Folders) (Map-case G-13, Drawer 8)
  - Taxes, 1874-1891 (Map-case G-13, Drawer 8)
  - Topographical and Oyster Maps (Mostly Tidewater Virginia) (Map-case 10, Drawer 15)
  - USDA Bureau of Soils, Soil Maps (Numerous States, includes Key) (Map-case G-13, Drawer 9-10)